Kotschnig, Walter Maria; Papers ger053
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Manuscripts of speeches and lectures delivered by Walter M. Kotschnig, 1933-1976; Undated; 4; 191 folders
  - "Mount Holyoke Appeal", 1942 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 131)
  - "Commemoration of Czech University". Smith, 1942 November 19 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 132)
  - "Re-Education of Youth After the War". National Council for the Social Studies, New York, 1942 November 28 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 133)
  - "The Lessons of a Year". Pearl Harbor Commemoration, 1942 December 08 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 134)
  - "Dear Friends of the Masters School". Masters School, 1943 January 17 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 135)
  - "A World of Free Peoples: Europe". YWCA, Cleveland, 1943 January 23 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 136)
  - Untitled. Kiwanis, Grinnell, 1943 March 16 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 137)
  - Untitled. Grinnell High School, 1943 March 17 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 138)
  - "What Future for Germany?" Grinnell, 1943 March 17 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 139)
  - "Soviet Russia in War & Peace". Grinnell, 1943 March 22 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 140)
  - "The Period of Transition from War to Peace". Darien Republican Club, 1943 April 03 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 141)
  - "In Defense of the Liberal Arts", 1943 April 14 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 142)
  - "Our Attitude to Germany". Lansdowne, 1943 May 11 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 143)
  - "Chatham Hall Commencement", 1943 June 01 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 144)
  - "The Re-education of Germany". Univ. of Chicago, 1943 July 22 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 145)
  - "The Future of Europe". Smith Assembly, 1943 August 11 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 146)
  - "Planning for the Post-War World". Springfield, 1943 October 03 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 147)
  - Untitled. Grinnell, 1943 October 20 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 148)
  - "The Challenge to Education: The Fascist War on Civilization". Hartford Lecture Series, 1943 November 01 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 149)
  - "Students in the World Revolution". Los Angeles, 1943 November 20 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 150)
  - "WSSF Appeal, 1943". California, 1943 November 20-1943 November 30 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 151)
  - "Education for International Living". Great Neck, 1944 January 18 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 152)
  - "Britain & France in the World of Tomorrow". The Union, Boston, 1944 April 13 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 153)
  - "The U.S. in the Post-War World", 1944 April 20 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 154)
  - "Relations of the Proposed Educational & Cultural Organization to the Specialized International Agencies", 1945 September 22 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 155)
  - "Why an Organization on Education & Cultural Relations?", ca. 1945 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 156)
  - "UNESCO", 1945 December 12 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 157)
  - "Illusions and Realities of 1947". Rockford College, Rockford, IL, Undated (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 158)
  - "FAO & the United Nations", 1948 October 12 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 159)
  - "FAO and ILO Aiding Children & Youth", 1948 November 01 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 160)
  - "Freeing the Minds of Men". Fairmont, 1948 November 05 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 161)
  - "The Assault on Religion in Eastern Europe". Washington, D.C., 1949 November 10 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 162)
  - "Technical Assistance in Social Welfare to Underdeveloped Countries". Atlantic City, 1950 April 27 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 163)
  - "U.S. Participation in the U.N". St. Joseph's, Philadelphia, 1952 October 20 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 164)
  - "Soviet Propaganda". Smith College, 1953 February 18 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 165)
  - "Two Worlds in Conflict". George Williams College, Chicago, 1953 June 07 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 166)
  - "Foundations of the United Nations". Univ. of Kansas, 1954 January 25 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 167)
  - "Quotable Quotes on MSP", [ca. 1957] (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 168)
  - "International Aid for Underdeveloped Areas", 1958 January 31 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 169)
  - "Social Work in Today's World". Massachusetts Social Workers, 1959 November 05 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 170)
  - "Point Four and the Social Worker", [ca. 1959] (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 171)
  - "News Editors & Broadcasters", 1965 October 28 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 172)
  - "Problems of US Foreign Policy". Athens, OH, 1966 November 23 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 173)
  - "European Statisticians, 1968 May 16 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 174)
  - "2 Fronts". San Francisco, 1945, 1969 March 28 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 175)
  - "UN System: Specialized Agencies". Wilcox Seminar, 1970 April 13 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 176)
  - "Staff meeting 4/23/70: Capacity Study", Undated (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 177)
  - "The UN in Crisis". Friends Meeting, Florida Ave, 1976 January 04 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 178)
  - "American Citizen of the World". Middlefield, 1976 July 28 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 179)
  - Miscellaneous speaking notes, Undated (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 180)
  - Course lectures, 4.181 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ))
    - "Comparative Education II: Economic & Social Implications". Smith College, 1937 February-1937 May (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 181)
    - "Comparative Education II", Undated (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 182)
    - "History and Philosophy of Education". Mt. Holyoke, 1937-1938 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 183)
    - "History and Philosophy of Education". Reading lists, handouts, Undated (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 184)
    - "Youth Problems". Education 32b, Smith College, 1941 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 185)
    - "Problems of American Education". Education 41a, 1941-1942 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 186)
    - "Youth and Social Change". Springfield, 1941-1942 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 187)
      Harvard-Boston University Extension Courses.
    - Education 22a, Smith College, 1942-1943 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 188)
    - "Youth and Social Change". Education 32a, Smith College, 1943-1944 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 189)
    - "Post-War Education". Springfield, 1943-1944 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 190)
    - Examinations, 1937-1944 (Box 11 (4-Manuscripts of speeches and lectures ), Folder 191)
- Typescripts of books and articles authored by Walter M. Kotschnig, 1927-1977; 5; 147 folders
  This series contains typescripts of chapters of Kotschnig's Unemployment in the Learned Professions, his chapter contributions to the Brookings Institution study published under the title The United Nations and Promotion of the General Welfare, as well as typescripts of early articles in German, typescripts in English of numerous articles, speeches written for others (Secretary of State, Edward R. Stettinius, Jr.), and speeches delivered at official Department of State and United Nations functions (including speeches before the United Nations Economic and Social Council, UNESCO, The Economic Commission for Africa and the Far East, ECAFE, and The Economic Commission for Africa, ECA, sessions).
  - "Universalökonomie und Weltwirtschaft", Undated (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 1)
  - "Haben Sie gut geschlafen?", Undated (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 2)
  - "International Understanding and the Written Word", Undated (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 3)
  - "Fellow Students..." [Vox Studentium], Undated (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 4)
  - "The Youth Movement Explained". Review, ca. 1927 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 5)
  - "I.S.S. and the University". Mount Holyoke, 1931 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 6)
  - "The University in the Social Order". I.S.S. Annual Conference, Brno, Czechoslovakia, Undated (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 7)
  - "Die neue Sintflut". Annual report, 1933 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 8)
  - "The Overcrowding of the Universities and Unemployment among Graduates in Europe. Introductory Report", 1933 September 20-1933 September 22 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 9)
  - "Reflections on a Visit to Germany. May 1933", Undated (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 10)
  - "Can Education meet the Fundamental Needs of Society?" 13th Annual I.S.S. Conference, Bouffement, Undated (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 11)
  - "Six Thousand Eight Hundred Intellectuals in Exile from Germany", 1934 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 12)
  - "Political Leadership and the Universities", Undated (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 13)
  - "Christian Untouchables", 1935 November 20 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 14)
  - "Memo on Courses of Study in the Division of the Social Sciences", 1936 February (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 15)
  - "Notes on Dr. Kotschnig's Visit to U.S.A.", 1936 January 06-1936 March 10 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 16)
  - "Notes on Dr. Kotschnig's Visit to U.S.A.", 1936 March 11-1936 March 20 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 17)
  - "Notes on Dr. Kotschnig's Visit to the U.S.A.", 1936 March 23-1936 April 11 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 18)
  - "Notes on Dr. Kotschnig's Visit to the U.S.A.", 1936 April 13-1936 April 18 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 19)
  - "Notes on Dr. Kotschnig's Visit to U.S.A.", Winter 1936 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 20)
  - "Situations of and Opportunities for Displaced German Scholars in the United States. Report by Walter M. Kotschnig on his Visit to American Colleges and Universities, 1936 February 15-1936 April 24 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 21)
  - "Memo by Walter M. Kotschnig on Visit to Middle West, Pacific Coast and South", 1936 March 15-1936 April 25 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 22)
  - Unemployment in the Learned Professions. Part 1: "The Rush for Higher Education", 1937 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 23)
  - Unemployment in the Learned Professions. Part 2: "The Plight of the Learned Professions", 1937 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 24)
  - Unemployment in the Learned Professions. Part 3: "Counter-incomes", 1937 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 25)
  - Unemployment in the Learned Professions. Part 4: "Occupational and Educational Planning", 1937 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 26)
  - Unemployment in the Learned Professions. Corrections, Undated (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 27)
  - "Memorandum on Dr. Kotschnig's Study 'Unemployment in the Learned Professions'", 1937 November 01 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 28)
  - "Some Reflections on the Treatment of Jews and Non-Aryans in Germany and on the Measures Designed to Help Them", 1938 November (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 29)
  - World Education. Notes to issues, Undated (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 30)
  - The United Nations and Promotion of the General Welfare. Brookings Institution Study. "Tentative Outline", Undated (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 31)
  - The United Nations and Promotion of the General Welfare. "Introduction", Undated (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 32)
  - The United Nations and Promotion of the General Welfare. Chapter 1: "Scope and Limitation of International Action", Undated (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 33)
  - The United Nations and Promotion of the General Welfare. Chapter 2: "Organizational Developments: The United Nations and the Specialized Agencies", Undated (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 34)
  - The United Nations and Promotion of the General Welfare. Chapter 3: "The Problem of Coordination", Undated (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 35)
  - The United Nations and Promotion of the General Welfare. Chapter 4: "Techniques of International Cooperation in Economic, Social, and Related Fields", Undated (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 36)
  - The United Nations and Promotion of the General Welfare. Chapter 11: "Promotion of Higher Standards of Living", Undated (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 37)
  - The United Nations and Promotion of the General Welfare. Chapter 12: "Welfare and Social Defense", Undated (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 38)
  - The United Nations and Promotion of the General Welfare. Chapter 13: "Education, Science, and Culture", Undated (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 39)
  - The United Nations and Promotion of the General Welfare. Chapter 14: "Community Organization and Development", Undated (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 40)
  - "The National Mind -- English, French, German. By Michael Demiashkevich". Review, 1938 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 41)
  - "The Development of Education in the Twentieth Century. By Adolph E. Meyer". Review, 1939 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 42)
  - "Not by Arms Alone. By Hans Kohn". Review, 1940 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 43)
  - "Memorandum for a Committee of the United States Committee of International Student Service Engaged in Preparing a Volume on American Education", 1941 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 44)
  - "Proposed I.S.S. Publication on Higher Education in the U.S". Rockefeller Foundation project, 1941 June (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 45)
  - "The Educational Philosophy of National Socialism. By George Frederick Kneller". Review, 1941 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 46)
  - "Degrees for Exchange Students", Undated (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 47)
  - "Duggan, Stephen. A Professor at Large". Review, 1943 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 48)
  - "DeMarko, Roland R. The Italianization of African Natives". Review, 1943 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 49)
  - "Memorandum Regarding the Establishment of an International Division within the United States Office of Education", 1943 March (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 50)
  - "Proposal for the Training of Relief and Reconstruction Workers for Liberated Poland (to be offered at the Smith College Summer School 1943)", Undated (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 51)
  - "Education for a World Rebuilt". MacDonald College, Quebec, 1943 September 11 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 52)
  - "Lecture by Professor Kotschnig for the Commission to Study the Organization of Peace". New School for Social Research, 1944 February 10 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 53)
  - "Major Considerations in the Organization of Europe", 1944 July 26-1944 August 28 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 54)
  - "Problems of Educational Reconstruction", 1944 September (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 55)
  - "Draft Remarks Commanding Civic Organizations, etc. for Fostering Discussion of the Dumbarton Oaks Proposals", 1944 October (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 56)
  - Speeches written for the Under Secretary of State, Edward R. Stettinius, Jr., 5.57 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 57-67)
    - "Remarks of Edward R. Stettinius, Jr., (Under) Secretary of State, expressing his appreciation to New York University at the time of receiving an honorary degree of Doctor of Laws", 1944 October 18 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 57)
    - "Remarks of the Honorable Edward R. Stettinius, Jr. Acting Secretary of State, on the occasion of receiving an honorary degree of Doctor of Engineering from Stevens Institute of Technology", 1944 October 28 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 58)
    - "Remarks of the Honorable Edward R. Stettinius, Jr., Under Secretary of State, on VE-Day", 1944 November 11 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 59)
    - "Draft of Mr. Wilson's Address Before the Exports Managers Club and the National Foreign Creditors Managers Association, New York", 1944 November 14 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 60)
    - "Address on the Dumbarton Oaks Proposals by Mr. Edwin C. Wilson, Director of the Office of Special Political Affairs, Department of State", [November 1944] (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 61)
    - [Stettinius, Edward R., Jr.]. "To the American Foreign Service", 1944 November 25 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 62)
    - "Message to the League of Nations Association on the event of the 25th Anniversary celebration of the founding of the League of Nations", Undated (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 63)
    - [Stettinius, Edward R., Jr.]. "Opening Remarks of the Secretary of State at the Meeting of Magazine Editors and Writers, New York", 1944 December 08 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 64)
    - "Opening Remarks of the Secretary of State at the Meeting of the American Peace Society, Dumbarton Oaks", 1944 December 13 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 65)
    - "Statement by Secretary of State Edward R. Stettinius, Jr", 1945 March 05 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 66)
    - "First Draft of the Secretary's Remarks at the Second Meeting of the United Nations Conference on International Organization, San Francisco", 1945 April 26 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 67)
    - "Education and the United Nations". Association of American Colleges, Atlantic City, 1945 January 11 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 68)
    - "International Education". United Nations Conference, New Haven, 1945 January 12-1945 January 13 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 69)
    - "Visit to Atlantic City, New Haven, Connecticut, and Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania", 1945 January 17 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 70)
    - "Toward World Economic and Social Integration", 1949 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 71)
    - "Economic and Social Foundations of the United Nations", 1951 April 19-1951 April 20 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 72)
    - "United States Delegation to the United Nations Economic and Social Council. Thirteenth Session. Synopsis of Remarks in the Social Committee by the Honorable Walter Kotschnig, Deputy United States Representative to ECOSOC", 1951 August 01 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 73)
    - "Transcript of Remarks by the Honorable Walter Kotschnig, Deputy United States Representative, Responding to the Statements of Several Other Delegations on the Draft Convention on Freedom of Information", 1951 August 15 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 74)
    - "Statement by the Honorable Walter Kotschnig, Deputy Representative of the United States in the Economic and Social Council, on the World Social Situation", 1952 July 14 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 75)
    - "Challenge to UNESCO", 1954 March 03 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 76)
    - "Notes for Mr. Key's Speech in Miami", 1954 May 06 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 77)
    - "UNESCO National Commission action on security cases in UNESCO Secretariat", 1954 October 19 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 78)
    - "Attempted Communist Infiltration of World University Service", 1955 March 22 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 79)
    - "US Position at the UN Conference in Geneva on Proposed Slavery Convention", 1956 September 28 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 80)
    - "Allegations of Communist Infiltrations in the United Nations", 1957 September 30 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 81)
    - "Social Development and Foreign Policy", 1959 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 82)
    - "Ministry of Planning: Its Position Within the Royal Government of Afghanistan and Problems of Coordination and Coordination of Policies and Actions of the RGA regarding the Economic, Social, and Related Activities of the United Nations and other Inter-governmental Organizations". Kabul, Afghanistan, 1959 October 10 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 83)
    - "United Nations Decade of Development. Consultations in Paris and London, 1961 October (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 84)
      Report submitted by Walter M. Kotschnig, Director, Office of International Economic and Social Affairs.".
  - Economic Commission for Asia and the Far East (ECAFE) speeches, 5.58 (Box 12 (5-Typescripts of books and articles authored ), Folder 85-96)